Hey guys, we have another method to dumbbells as using the COM SCCS TLL.
Basically, this COM SCCS DLL will be located under the system 32 directory.
So, we can use the needM function from the COM SCCR DLL and we can dumb else as ok.
So, this technique is commonly followed by the detectors.
So, here you can find in the law-based project ok.
So, this method has been commonly used by the detectors to dumb panels as from an LSS process
from my machine.
So, let me give you some of the commands we can dumb, let me first you need the
pit of the LSS, so I have used the task list and pipe command to find the LSS pit of the
process.
It is an 840.
So, once you find the LSS pit, you can use the rendial32.exe with the COM SCCS DLL and
needM function and pit of LSS and directly to save the LSS file dumb file, you can use
the command to dumb panels as ok.
Previously, this method has been method has worked, but nowadays method was not working.
And I just dig into the COM SCCS DLL, so here you can find the COM SCCS DLL.
I have opened through the PEBIR and I find the function has been changed to mini dump
W, I have used, let me use this function mini dump W, let me try whether it was working
or not.
Even though it was not working, the Microsoft took some options in the COM SCCS DLL to stop
dumpling ok, so if you notice this kind of commands in any of the older version of windows
or anything, so this could be a harmful thread because we can use our rendial32 and COM
SCCS DLL, the login to dump and LSS from the machine ok, this will be a very sensitive
one ok.
Cool guys, let us stop off and we will continue our discussion next video see you bye bye.